I forgot to mention that the other day I was walking through the airport and a brother,
I was actually walking very fast through an airport because I was late for my connecting
flight.
And a brother was like, excuse me, excuse me, miss, excuse me.
And I was like, I'm late.
So like, if you want to walk with me, walk with me.
And he was like, excuse me, excuse me.
And I was like, I'm late for my flight.
And then he flashed his badge.
So then I stopped because now I'm dealing with fucking badges being flashed.
And he walks up to me and says, keep up the good work.
And y'all, when I tell you I lost my mind, I was like, don't you flash your fucking badge
at me to get me to stop.
And he was like, I'm still a regular person.
I said, no, don't fucking waste my time.
I thought you was about to say some shit to me that I needed to hear.
Are you out of your goddamn mind?
I said all of this, of course, while I was going to my gate.
But yes, use his badge to get me to stop, even though I was running to a flight to compliment
me.
And people wonder why we say fuck the police.
Mm, mm, mm.